<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
    <HDH_BasicDensity.label>basic-density hydroponics</HDH_BasicDensity.label>
    <HDH_BasicDensity.description>Develops the first generation of dense, multi-layer hydroponic infrastructure. Unlocks the basic-density hydroponics bay, a compact 1x4 basin that supports 16 plants and provides roughly four times the growing area in the same footprint. It can rely on sunlight or enable a built-in sun lamp at extra power cost, but it still requires steady power and does not regulate temperature.</HDH_BasicDensity.description>

    <HDH_HighDensity.label>high-density hydroponics</HDH_HighDensity.label>
    <HDH_HighDensity.description>Refines tray stacking, nutrient circulation, and lighting control for industrial dense farming. Unlocks the high-density hydroponics bay, a 2x4 basin that supports 80 plants and provides roughly ten times the growing area in the same footprint. It can rely on sunlight or enable a built-in sun lamp at extra power cost, but it still requires steady power and does not regulate temperature.</HDH_HighDensity.description>

    <HDH_HighDensity_Ultra.label>ultra-density hydroponics</HDH_HighDensity_Ultra.label>
    <HDH_HighDensity_Ultra.description>Pushes dense hydroponic engineering into advanced materials and large-scale environmental support. Unlocks the ultra-density hydroponics bay, a 2x6 basin that supports 240 plants and provides roughly twenty times the growing area in the same footprint. It can rely on sunlight or enable a built-in sun lamp at extra power cost, but it still requires steady power and does not regulate temperature.</HDH_HighDensity_Ultra.description>

    <HDH_HighDensity_Quantum.label>quantum-density hydroponics</HDH_HighDensity_Quantum.label>
    <HDH_HighDensity_Quantum.description>Applies quantum field manipulation to collapse multiple growth layers into a single compact chamber. Unlocks the quantum-density hydroponics bay, a 2x2 spacer-grade basin whose capacity scales with power and which can enable a built-in sun lamp at extra power cost while still ignoring ordinary temperature limits.</HDH_HighDensity_Quantum.description>
</LanguageData>
